Mom, Dad
What are you doing
I
We're checking on you
To see if you need any help
Right
Mixing the feed alone
Is so exhausting
We'll help you
That's great
Actually, there is something
I need help with
It's just a bit dirty and tiring
We're not afraid
Hard work is nothing
As long as we get the formula
Daniel's hand
Will be saved
Exactly
We're not afraid of work
Just leave the work to us
You just focus on mixing
I've already mixed the secret feed
Mix
You finished it
Yeah
The secret feed
Needs to be
Regular feed
Mixed in proportion
I was worried
Doing it alone
I couldn't mix it all
You can help me
Mix it into that pile
This much
Needs to be mixed
Exactly
To make sure it's mixed well
Every bit has to be turned over
No slacking off
Thanks for the hard work, Mom, Dad
Good luck